The Nighttime and Idol Conversation Series has begun, and I'm Akimoto Noka, Team President, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm Aika Akimoto, the president of Team Akimoto, and I'm Aika Aiya, the fourth member of the team.
Aika, it's the first time we've had a proper talk at Aika's, the first time I've been in front of so many dreams, I'm embarrassed to say.
I've never been in front of a dream like this before I'm so embarrassed I don't know what to call you
I'm Ho-chan, Ho-chan... please call me Ho-chan...
I'm Ai-kaman and I'm Ho-chan, and we'd like to start off by presenting a project that will help us get to know each other better.
Special talk session between Akimoto Nika and Aikaman
Talk session
Talk session... what's that for the first time?
Shion-san organizes a special music session with a variety of guests to discuss various topics prepared by the staff.
We two will share our opinions on various themes prepared by the staff and come up with a single answer.
It's going to get deeper and deeper, and I'm even happier this time.
Thank you very much for coming, Mr. Kettle of the kettle, and for holding the Aikaman.
Is that hot water? Is it hot water?
Can I ask you to draw the answer? Then open it.
You don't want me to see it, right? Oh, it's okay.
It's okay, it's kind of okay, it's full of stuff.
Okay, next. Here we go. Durung.
I can see a little.
I wonder... when I watch other idols perform, I pay attention to the zeros.
Oh, it's hard to tell.
You might be interested in that.
It's true. What do people look for?
But I'm curious about it all, aren't I?
But I'm trying to find something I don't have.
Idols are always shining no matter where you look.
I guess each group has a different concept.
By the way, what kind of concept do you have? Zion is a unit that combines instrumentalists and vocalists.
We are a concept group called "Zion", so we have a lot of flexibility and strength of sound.
We have a wide range of cool and cute songs with a mature sound.
Our concept is to give a performance that stands out from the background of idols.
It's true that it's hard to find idols who can play, especially if they're one of our members.
But I'm not a vocalist or anything like that, but I can play a musical instrument, and I can wear the clothes of that instrument and dance.
The way of rhythm and the way of dance are different... idols can dance freely without instruments... but we have to do it with a big instrument.
Idols can dance freely without instruments, but they can't just do it with a big instrument, so they have to watch their dance moves.
She said she studies a lot.
That's a great way to look at it, isn't it?
I wonder where she's going with it.
But I might look at formations.
There are some formations that only one person can do.
We are a group of four, so four people are limited in formations.
That's true.
That's why... look at Momokuro-chan's Momokuro-chan.
I've heard that even with four members, there are so many ways to showcase formations.
You might see that too.
Just because they all have the same formation, you can tell they've practiced a lot.
It's a sign that they've been practicing.
They don't line up, normally.
Because there are four of them.
Because four people don't always line up.
That's right.
That's why you can tell they're really working hard.
That's what I always think.
I've seen on YouTube, during the trip to Okinawa...
We all saw Sachi's live performance.
This is cool, I love this song.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much!
I know this is totally off topic, but...
I'll do it right at the show.
I always do it right.I always get it right.
It's very personal.
Formation
I have all the formations.
Formation?
When I watch other idols perform live, I pay attention to their formation.
formation
That's right!
Yay!
It was formation.
That's kind of interesting, isn't it?
I want to do the next one.
Next one, next one.
Next!
What do you like?
I'm scared.
What?
I've been thinking about social networking...
Oh my God, I don't know what I'm doing. What am I going to do?
What do you do on social networking sites?
Twitter, Instagram, TikTok...
I'm on Twitter, Instagram, TikTok... but I don't really use them all that much.
What do you do most often? Well, I guess Twitter.
Is it because Twitter is easy to use because it's just text?
I think Twitter is the best because it's all text.
I can tweet anything when I feel like it. I tend to rely on Twitter a lot.
I tweet everything.
Whenever I feel something, I tweet it.
I don't get many likes.
It doesn't matter. It's like a social networking site where you just go with your feelings.
That's true. But idols are so cute.
I love pictures of idols that are cute and cute. I love pictures like that.
But I have an image of idols who love cute pictures or pictures that make you feel really hot.
I can't do that so much, and recently a member told me about it.
I was told by a member that I should post lots of cute pictures.
I've been trying to be more conscious of that lately.
But I'm not insta-less.
I'm only on Instagram.
That's right.
But when it comes to Instagram, I can't just casually and immediately post something.
It's difficult, isn't it?
That's true.
Are there any girls you're conscious of?
Not really.
I post it as soon as I put it on a good ice cream.
What's that? I'm curious.
Yeah, I'm curious.
Is that okay?
That's fine.
It's good.
But it's important to be emotionally rich and put it on the page.
If you keep going...
That's what I think, too.
When you find a delicious ice cream, it's important to put it on the site as it is.
So it's important to be emotionally rich.
That's what I think, too.
I know it's a bit forced, but...
Let's go with that.Let's go with that.
So that's the type of people we are.
Emotionally rich.
Okay, then.
You're getting more and more determined, aren't you?
What we're conscious of on social networking sites is that we're
be emotionally rich.
It was
That's nice.
It's a little bit forced.
All right.
Very nice.
Thank you.
I wonder if it's still good.
I'm scared. I don't know.
I don't know what it's like. I'm going. It's the first time I've been to a concert and I'm worried about being a 00.
I wanted to do this. You wanted to do this? I wanted this to be there.
You mean there is one? Yes. Aren't you worried about the mic?
The mics are different. Some venues have big mics.
You used to almost slip and fly off the stage once?
That's dangerous! I'm sorry, Mr. Pie! I'm sorry!
That's right. Microphones have sponges on them.
Like outside venues or idol festivals.
They're there to make it look like a satellite, so they can film it quickly and then move on to the next one.
It makes a big difference.
It's so different. I met someone who understands me for the first time.
Oh, my God! I'm so curious about that.
But they're pom-poms. I'm not conscious of them.
It's not that I'm conscious of it, it's just that it's not a venue, or a festival.
I'm really allergic to house dust.
So sometimes I get really sensitive to house dust.
The moment I enter the room, I get so itchy, everyone starts taking medicine.
Oh no! You're the first to know.
Is everyone that sensitive today?
Are you that sensitive?
Does it depend on the venue?
Sometimes it is, but I'm just really sensitive.
Does it go down your throat?
No, not my throat.
I have a strong throat.
It's just a scratchy throat.
That's very important.
Important?
Oh, my God. I have hay fever, too.
When there's pollen.
Outside.
I can't do it anymore. It's too much.
So no hay fever.
I can't go out on stage.
I won't be able to go out.
I can't go outside.
Then I can't go outside.
Dusty NG, dusty NG, itchy, itchy, itchy, itchy.
Even if you do it at that venue...
It depends on the day.
It's difficult
But it's important
It's important
The conditions are important.
And don't you worry about the location of the meeting city?Also, don't you care about the location of Aiai City?
It's very important.
Hui-machi...
There's a speaker that only we can hear.
We have our own speakers.
There's a separate speaker for the audience.
There was one for us.
I don't know...
and the sound that the audience hears
It's totally different.
So when I said I couldn't hear anything at all at the meeting
The manager said
It's fine when we can rehearse.
But when you can't rehearse for an event or something...
Manager...
"Kakka, kakka, kakka, kakka.
It's fine when they watch you.
But when they don't...
Or they don't look at you.
It happens, doesn't it?
Yes, it happens.
Of course.
I'm trying my best, but the majors...
It's important.
That's important, isn't it?
Sound matters
Sound is important.
Sound?
Is it acoustics?
That's where the microphones go.
Sound.
We're professionals.
So, what's the first time you've opened a show?
I'm concerned about the sound.
Is the sound.
Cool.
Nice.
Earlier, social networking is an emotional
but it's not.
It's totally different.
It sounded
Cool.
Here.
Here you go.
Scary.
Den!
When I receive a demo of a new song, I'm concerned about ____.
It's difficult.
Eh, I wonder what it is.
When you make a new song or record it, do you have the parts allocated from the beginning?
At first, it is not decided, and then the song is written. Then we listen to it together and say, "This is the song,
Then we listen to the song together and agree on the parts.
You assigned the parts before recording?
Yes, we did.
That's right! So that's the type of person you are!
Oh, you're not?
You take all the parts, all the members, and then you decide what's the best part?
I just said, "This girl fits this part,
Wow! What's that?
You just guessed,I have to guess,
Oh, so I have to sing the whole song?
Yes.
Oh, no!
No!
I didn't know there was such a way.
That's the way to do it. But I thought that was pretty much the way it was.
But it's because there are only two of us.
I see, with two people,
With two people, there are almost all the parts,
I see. But if it's just the two of us, why not just take it all?
That's true. But it happens quite often.
In the end, the vocalists are very close to each other,
They are very close with each other, and they confess to each other in this way,
So they end up changing the parts from the ones they've been asked to play,
Maybe it's better that way. So maybe it's better that way.
But in the sense that I can concentrate on that part and practice.
That's true.
It's possible.
But let's try that next time.
You want to try it?
You want to try?
Please do.
What's on your mind?
Let's see.
I'd like to sing around here,
But yes.
I might be interested in the parts that are easy to sing,
And after that, I'm sure I'll get a call here.
After the call is opened, I will want to call for it,
I might imagine if they would call out here or there.
It's amazing, isn't it? Sacchan's call.
Really?
That's amazing. I want to do it too, Aiko.
Want to?
I want to do it.
I want you to do it. I want you to do it.
It's difficult. Between the calls.
But, you know, even if we perform it for the first time, they'll still come in,
Yes, it's amazing. It's amazing, isn't it?
Is it in my blood?
I don't know if it's in my DNA,
It's like I was born with it.
There must be something about you. Idol fans,
It's in my blood.
Yes. It's like, "This is the place to be.
But everyone can tell, can't they?
I know.
Why is that? Is it because they are trained? Or something.
Already.
Maybe.
Throat.
Throat and.
It might.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What was that?
I'm curious about this. I'll be curious when I get the demos of the new songs.
But the new 4 has solo parts for the instruments.
So, it's alto saxophone, euphonium, piano, and twin vocals,So, I guess it's because we have an alto saxophone, euphonium, piano, and twin vocals,
They all have different personalities,
That's very stylish.
Thank you very much.
So each of us has a part that stands out,
I would like to sing here, or there should definitely be a prominent part for each of the five members.
It would be nice.
Yes, that's right.
Depending on the song, you may want to feature this girl.
Yes, there are. Yes, there are.
But I'm still very concerned about making sure that everyone has a prominent part so that they don't get overshadowed,
So it's all about parts.
Parts.
Part.
It's a part.
Part part part,
Important, important, important.
Everyone is important.
Not just me.
That's right.
All four of us have our own unique singing styles, voices, and singing styles, and they are all so different from each other,
But I began to understand that the singers were made with the image of this part of the song in mind from the beginning,
I began to understand.
I can understand.
Yes. It's important to have a part.
Then, let's make it a part.
Yes.
When you receive a demo of a new song, what do you care about?
Parts.
There is a part.
It's a part.
It was a part.
Yes, it is.
There is.
It is so.
Love is so.
That's right.
Everyone wants to stand out.
Then the last.
Rast.
Last.
I'll pull it out.
What's the last one? What's left?
Okay, let's go.
What do we have?
There are 00 things you should take with you on a live concert expedition.
We have a lot of these.
Quick, quick.
Gummi gummi gummi.
What?
Gummi.
Gummi?
I brought three today.
Is that for when you get hungry?
I'd get excited if I had gummy bears.
I'll give them to you later.
Thank you.
I have a lot of them.
They're cute.Cute.
ShinonThere have been more and more expeditions recently, and I travel by car a lot.
So we spend a lot of time in the car, and I feel sorry for the driver,
We didn't have anything to do, so we just stayed in the back and ate gummy bears,
We would exchange gummy bears.
You are the one who eats these.
But we definitely have gummy bears in the lesson room.
I guess you could say that,
When we have lessons, the manager prepares drinks and stuff,
And there are gummy bears there too.
Do the staff prepare them for you?
Gummi.
Thank you.
To keep our spirits up.
For the lesson.
Yes.
There are gummies on the table.
That's genius.
I wish we could do that.
Why?
I've been punished.
It's got a message, too. There are gummy bears called "Tough Gummies,
I think they're telling us to be tough.
That's sweet.
Please do it.
They said they won't do it.
They won't do it.
Leave it to the four members.
Maybe if I do it, they'll all be happy.
Later, this is also important.
Like a pillow.
For your neck.
For sleeping.
I have it ready.
I bought it recently.
I used to be a bad sleeper,
I've been such a bad sleeper,
I really like it when I put it on.
I know it's good, but it's a burden.
That's right.
I always leave it in the car somewhere.
I don't take it home because it's in the way.
If you have a car for transportation, you can just leave it there.
But also when I don't use it,
I kick it with my foot or something.
I take good care of them.
It's in good condition, so you have to take good care of it.
That's true.
But that might be a good idea.
Expedition.
I think the fans would be interested in that.
There are fans who travel to the show.
I keep an extension cord in my carry-on.
That's very helpful.
It's nice when it's right here on the bed.
An outlet.
I can charge my batteries while I sleep.
But when it's only over here on my desk.
It's very far away, right?
It's very far away, isn't it?
If you have an extension cord,With an extension cord,
I can sleep with my phone next to me and charge it while I sleep.
I can sleep.
Sure.
Is it expensive?
An extension cord?
I don't think it's expensive.
Then buy it.
Buy it.
Let's make it an extension cord and gummies.
Let's do that.
Extension cords and gummi.
Then, please.
Yes.
What should we bring on a live concert expedition?
Is an extension cord and gummy bears.
That was it.
You had a lot of sessions, didn't you?
I'm glad. We had a lot of sessions.
So, how was it? Try it.
It was fun. I wanted to do three more questions.
I wanted to.
I want to do it, too.
I want to.
It was interesting to hear different opinions.
But the concept of the group was also different,
I felt that what they were looking for and what they were conscious of were also different.
That's right.
So they are different.
But that's what makes it interesting. Idols are interesting.
They are interesting. There are a tremendous number of idols, aren't there?
That's right. I noticed that the number of idols has increased a lot.
That's right. It's amazing these days, isn't it?
There are so many.
They are really cute.
Every single one of them is big and cute.
I wanted to tell you all about them.
I'm sure you get the message.
But they're really cool.
I'm glad.
It's really cool.
That's why you're good-looking.
I got it back. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I would like to talk to you again about our growing friendship.
Tomorrow will be the second part of the dialogue. Please look forward to that as well.
So far, we have had Honoka Akimoto of Team Shachi and Yuka Kino of Sheyan,
and Yuka Kino of Sheyan.
See you tomorrow!
Bye bye!